bitdefender.net 2014-12-26

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

BITDEFENDER is very cautious about how your information is collected when you surf our websites and enter information about yourself and how this information is used and shared with others. We appreciate your trust and it is very important to us. This notice describes our privacy policy. BY VISITING ANY OF OUR WEBSITES, YOU AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT. The information that you give us helps us personalize and continually improve your experience with us. 

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way for responding to your requests, improving our website, customizing future shopping and services for you, and to communicate with you for special offers, bonuses, sales, and related marketing information and activities. 

We use the so-called "cookies" and we obtain certain type of information when your Web browser accesses our services. We often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from any of our online services. We may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries of BITDEFENDER, business partners or affliliated companies. 

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other companies or entities. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the unlikely event that BITDEFENDER or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information might be one of the transferred assets. We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of BITDEFENDER, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

We work to protect the security of your information during any data transmission. 

This Privacy Statement may be subject to change without notice. This notice will still govern your use of our services and it is your responsibility to review them for any occurring changes. 

BITDEFENDER does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use the services, products and offers only with involvement and approval of a parent. 

If you choose to visit our Web site and use our services in any way, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Romania. Our business changes constantly. This Privacy Statement and the Conditions of use will change too and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. You should check our Web site frequently to see any new changes.
